vumber.com 2017-06-06

# Vumber - Virtual Number Privacy Statement

This privacy policy covers how we treat the personal information that we collect and receive when you subscribe for and use our services. This Policy explains the practices that apply to your personal Information.

### Collection of Your Personal Information

In order to provide services, Vumber must collect your personal phone number so we can identify you when you interact with our system, and to route telephone calls from other users to your phone. We never, under any circumstances, reveal your phone number to other Vumber users.

### How Your Personal Information Is Used

Your Personal Information is used to operate the service features and offerings, to personalize the services provided to you, and to communicate with you and respond to your inquiries.

Your Personal Information will never be shared with third parties except to provide the services that you have requested.

Vumber is not to be used for illegal activity. In the event that legal authorities deem it necessary to investigate a Vumber user's activity, by way of legal processes (court order, search warrant or subpoena), we will oblige as required by law.

We may use cookies, web beacons or similar technologies to enhance and personalize your experience with the Vumber services. This includes helping authenticate your identity when you login to Vumber; remembering your preferences and registration information; and measuring and researching the effectiveness of the Vumber services and promotions.

In the event Vumber is acquired, consolidates or merges with another company, that company will be bound by the terms and conditions of this privacy policy.

### Our Commitment to Security

We are committed to keeping your Vumber information private, and will use that information only for purposes of operating Vumber services and improving them. We have implemented security guidelines to help safeguard the privacy of your Vumber information from unauthorized access or improper use.

### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the Vumber Privacy Policy or its implementation, you can send email to [info@vumber.com](mailto:info@vumber.com)

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please review this Policy periodically at [www.vumber.com](http://www.vumber.com/) We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time.
